Show yourself, Leon!
Reborn
to Master the Blade
From Hero-King to Extraordinary Squire
Episode 3   Setting Out for the Capital
Yo.
Is that an Artifact?
Do you mean to betray us?
Something like that, yes.
When you said you'd lick a Highlander's
boots if you had to, that wasn't a joke?
Is he planning to stop us from hurting Rahl
as a way to win the Highlander's favor?
Don't be stupid. Of course it was a joke.
I'm a holy knight, you know.
I'm ready to throw away my life
for the people of this nation.
You saw what happened, right?
Right now, the Highlanders can do
whatever they want, and no one
on the surface can stop them.
It's a holy knight's duty
to protect the people, right?
But I can't do shit. And it makes me sick.
But without the Highland's help,
we can't protect the surface nations
from the magicite beasts!
There's some things
we just have to accept...
I don't like that.
I don't want either the Highlanders or the
magicite beasts hurting innocent people.
And there's a way to stop them?
Ever heard of the Bloodchain Brigade?
No.
An anti-Highland guerrilla organization.
In other countries, Highlanders
have destroyed entire towns
after the Brigade killed
one of their number.
All they do is spread chaos!
You're only seeing one side of the story.
The real goal of the Bloodchain Brigade
is to turn their blood to chains of iron
and drag the Highland down to earth.
So you'll defeat the Highlanders,
steal their technology, and spread
it among the people on the surface?
You're a smart one.
That way, we can keep ourselves safe
from the magicite beasts
without needing to suck up
to the Highlanders to do it.
The ideal outcome, don't you think?
And that's why you decided to betray us?
They've been trying to
recruit me for a while,
and what happened tonight
was the push I needed.
You can't fight the Highland and win!
And that's why I wanted
to bring you with me.
If they can get a Hyral Menas to research,
they might be able to discover how to make
Artifacts without the Highlanders' help.
No.
I refuse to take part in something that will
lead countless people to their deaths!
Want to come with me, Inglis?
I must decline.
So you're like Eris? You want
to keep things as they are?
Nope! But the way I see it, if I side with
Eris, I might get a chance to fight you!
S-She's crazy...
I can understand what you're saying.
But I've stopped connecting
power with justice.
I've lived one life that way already.
If you want to take Eris, come and get her!
I saw enough of that last fight
to tell you're strong.
It's hard to believe a cute little girl
can be so tough.
As an adult, I should go easy on you,
but I'll give you all I've got!
Be careful!
That's a high-rank Artifact that Leon's got!
It has a gift that allows it
to command lightning beasts!
By my eye, about thirty.
Two of you, follow me.
The rest, go get Inglis.
Eris is injured.
He means to stall me, and then spirit
her away while I am thus occupied.
A shrewd stratagem!
If you hit them with a strong attack,
they'll explode!
You sliced it in half? From that distance?
Next time we fight, use that skill!
No!
I'm not like you!
I don't fight because I enjoy it!
You can't fire that one off
that often, can you?
You used it just to tell
Inglis to be careful, huh?
That was nice of you.
So you're a tsundere, huh?
Shut up!
Oh, I hadn't realized!
Hang on! I'll come help you!
Idiot! I just said...
Wh-What happened?
What's going on?
I figured it out, Eris!
If you can't dodge their
explosions at close range,
then you just need to boost
your defense so much...
that the explosions don't hurt you, right?
I was trying to tell you
to attack from a distance!
This is faster, though!
I can surround myself with waves of
compressed aether—an Aether Shell—
to absorb the blast wave from the explosions!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
You're dreadful.
How could you tell me to use my full strength
when you weren't using yours?
That's not true.
The flaw in this technique is that
it can't be maintained for long.
You're incredible, kid.
I don't think either Eris or I
could handle you alone.
Which means you're a monster
on par with a Prismer.
Yes! I'm training to get to the point
where I can defeat one on my own!
Are you serious?
It's good to dream big!
Maybe you'll be invincible in the future,
but for now, I'm just going to
hope that you've got a weakness.
For example, you can't keep that little
trick of yours up for long, can you?
He's sharp. And strong of conviction.
In my previous life, he would have
been one of my most trusted men.
And if that's true?
What else? We see who breaks first!
Not happening.
Seriously?
It's not nice to stare at a girl's legs.
You're the one shoving them in my face!
I said, not happening!
Rani!
A magicite beast!
I won't let her be harmed!
I will protect Rani, no matter what!
To master the blade, I decided to
live this life beholden to none...
But this is the one promise I made to myself!
My vow as "Inglis Eucus"!
Rani, are you okay?
Thank you, Chris!
What are you doing here?
It wouldn't be right to make you
do this all by yourself!
So I was going to go on ahead
and teach Rahl a lesson myself.
But when I was inside, waiting,
he suddenly started to scream in pain,
and then he turned into that thing...
That's Rahl?
Inglis!
That's my name...
But how?
I've never heard of a human
becoming a magicite beast!
I drugged him.
Leon!
What do you mean?
It's called Prism Powder.
A drug made of condensed
Prism Flow, they said.
The Bloodchain Brigade created it.
They gave me some last time
they tried to recruit me.
It's harmless to surface people,
but if you use it on a Highlander...
Well, you can see for yourselves.
There's no way to cure him?
Of course not.
He deserves a miserable death, in any case.
Anyway, I'll be going.
Between you and Inglis, he's no threat.
Explode!
He got away.
What's going on?
Why is Leon...
I'll explain later.
Inglis!
It may be what he deserves, but I still
feel pity seeing him in this state.
I'll at least put you down
without making you suffer!
Chris!
There's only one way
to end this in a single strike.
But if were to do that here,
it would raze not only the mansion
but also a large chunk of the town.
Is there a means by which
the townsfolk may be spared?
That's it!
Rafinha! Inglis!
Are you all right?
Father! You came!
I'm sorry! I was wrong!
I should never have left the two of you
to shoulder this on your own!
Inglis!
A magicite beast?
Don't let it leave the grounds!
Split up!
Wait!
Eris is going to help us!
Eris!
What are you planning on doing?
Follow my lead!
We'll kick it!
Inglis!
I-It landed all the way out of the city.
Way to go, Eris!
You're so powerful!
What are you saying?
I'm not strong enough to kick it that far.
Follow. My. Lead.
Now, let's finish this!
Inglis!
It's still standing.
What was that you just did?
You made it look like I was
the one who kicked it...
Chris doesn't want people
knowing about her power.
If people knew there was somebody who could
defeat a magicite beast without a Rune,
it would cause chaos, she says.
I see.
That's the excuse I gave her,
but the truth is, I just don't want to be
stuck with the duty of protecting the town!
So, what do we do?
Eris, is that magicite beast
as strong as a Prismer?
No.
It's strong, I think, but it's like the
difference between an adult and a child.
So I need to be able to defeat it in
one hit if I want to fight a Prismer.
Chris!
What are you doing?
Just watch!
Inglis!
What is that power she's using?
It's been twelve years since then...
This is the perfect chance to test the power
I've spent this whole time training!
Inglis!
Rahl... Goodbye.
Aether...
Strike!
W-Wow!
That's my Chris!
Chris!
You okay?
I'm a little tired, I think.
I don't have enough stamina.
Gotta train more.
You're crazy...
What you said was right, Rani.
What did I say?
If you make a wish upon the Highland,
it'll come true.
Today's fight was a pretty good one.
I'll tell everyone that
this was Leon's doing,
and that he betrayed us
for the Bloodchain Brigade.
I'll make sure nobody blames you or Ymir.
Please do!
And tell everyone that it was you
who defeated the magicite beast, too.
Well, if that's what you want, but...
But?
You owe me one.
Repay that debt someday.
Okay, got it!
Goodbye.
Um, may I ask something?
What is it?
When we were introduced at the party,
you seemed upset about something.
Why was that?
Sorry.
You may find out someday,
but I don't want to say it.
I don't want people finding out
if I can help it.
Here I go, Chris!
Okay, Rani!
Rafinha   Age 15
Wow!
I doubled the number of arrows, too!
Yeah! Your bow's getting
stronger and stronger!
Inglis   Age 15
It's worth dodging!
What does "worth dodging" mean?
Oh, it's time to go!
No way! I'm not packed!
On this day, 15-year-old Inglis and
Rafinha would set out for the capital.
Rani, you silly girl.
They were to enroll in the knights'
academy in the capital city of Kyral.
Take good care of Rafinha.
I will, Your Grace!
If any boys go after her, drive them off!
Leave it to me!
Rafinha would train to be a knight,
and Inglis, to be her squire.
They would leave behind the home
they'd known for their whole lives,
and take the month-long
journey to the capital.
Town of Nova
The ruler of this town is a Highlander?
Yup. They just took over last year.
And they haven't done
anything terrible, right?
Not at all!
If anything, life's better
than it was under our last ruler.
All the townspeople are grateful.
I see...
I guess not all Highlanders are bad.
Yeah.
Traveling is so fun!
There's so much good food everywhere!
Yup.
But if we don't cut back a little,
we're going to run low on funds.
Huh? But it's only been ten days
since we left Ymir!
This is because you eat so much, Chris.
You too! You eat enough
for four people every meal!
But without money, we can't
eat yummy food on our trip!
Why not go help at the castle?
The castle?
Our ruler is hiring knights and mercenaries
to help with magicite beast attacks.
You two are both knights,
or so it seems to me.
They're hiring mercenaries, huh?
Sounds like a job for us!
This feels so good!
The hiring exam was easy, huh?
Sure was.
We just had to fight a few knights.
They're giving us the good guest rooms, too!
And the bath is huge!
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Something has been bothering me
ever since I arrived.
The flow of mana seems strange.
It's like a small amount of mana is being
drawn away from beneath everyone's feet.
Like it's being drained...
Chris, I'll wash your back!
O-Okay!
You're so lucky, Chris.
You have big breasts, and they're so pretty!
And a nice round butt, too!
Don't say that... It's embarrassing.
I've got the body of a little girl.
So I'm jealous!
It's not fair.
They're so big and soft!
I wish mine were like that!
Let me go!
You look like you're having fun.
Good evening.
G-Good evening.
What's wrong?
You're a Highlander?
Yes. I'm sorry for not
introducing myself earlier.
I'm the magistrate of Nova, Seilyn.
"Magistrate"? You're the town's ruler!
I-I'm sorry!
So this bath is for the ruler?!
We didn't know...
It's fine.
I heard that a knight with a Greater Rune
and another warrior had arrived,
so I wanted to meet them.
Lady Seilyn!
We want to take a bath too!
Rino! Miyumi! Chiko!
You know better than to interrupt
our ruler when she's talking!
It's alright, Mimoza.
Come in, girls!
Okay!
Me first!
No, me!
Wait!
Those kids...
I know it must be hard for you.
Not at all. I only have a son of my own,
so it's nice to have little girls around.
Those girls...
They're orphans. I couldn't just
leave them on the streets.
Wow, that's wonderful!
That's how a true ruler should be!
Thank you.
Um, I have a question.
Go ahead.
The flow of mana in this city
seems strange, somehow.
Is there a reason for that?
I'm sorry. I don't know anything about that.
I see.
If there's some powerful warrior
underground draining everyone's power,
I hope I get to fight them!
How long will you be staying?
We can't stay that long.
We'll be enrolling in the knights' academy
in the capital.
I see.
Is that a problem?
There's something I'd like your help with.
Just say the word!
If there's something we can help with...
Even if it involves fighting not
magicite beasts but people?
The knights who served under the
old ruler were a wicked bunch,
and I fired them all a little while ago.
Their violence toward the
townspeople had become a problem.
They've all joined together,
and they seem to be planning something.
Some of the knights I send out
on patrol have been attacked.
I want to deal with them all at once,
before something happens to
endanger the townspeople.
I know where their hideout is.
Chris...
There's one hundred, at a minimum.
There he is!
I knew if I caused enough trouble
in town, you'd come eventually.
Welcome.
Hawker, the last knight commander.
He's the leader.
You can't possibly beat this many,
Miss High-and-Mighty Highlander.
Quality over quantity!
Chris, preemptive attack!
Don't kill them, okay, Rani?
I'll just blow them all away!
Wh-What? A Greater Artifact?
Burst!
Sorry. I'm going to have to take you down.
Lament your own poor fortune
that I happened to be here today.
This intensity... It's just like Eris!
She's a Hyral Menas!
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
First Day
of their
Journey
to the
Capital
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Their
Wallets
Take a
Critical
Hit
Traveling is so fun!
Comic by Kuromura Moto